The Name Is Legendary. The Man Is Real.
Wild Bill is a western, action, drama film directed by Walter Hill.
Biopic about famous gunslinger Wild Bill Hickock.
The early career of legendary lawman is telescoped and culminates in his
relocation in Deadwood and a reunion with Calamity Jane.
Wild Bill Hickok, played by Jeff Bridges.
Calamity Jane, played by Ellen Barkin.
Charley Prince, played by John Hurt.
Susannah Moore, played by Diane Lane.
Buffalo Bill Cody, played by Keith Carradine.
Jack McCall, played by David Arquette.
Wild Bill is a 1995 American biographical Western film about the
last days of legendary lawman Wild Bill Hickok.
The film was written and directed by Walter Hill, and based on the 1978 stage play
Fathers and Sons by Thomas Babe and the 1986 novel Deadwood by Pete Dexter.
It stars Jeff Bridges, Ellen Barkin, John Hurt, and Diane Lane, and
was released by United Artists on December 1, 1995.
It was a box-office bomb, grossing $2.1 million on a budget of $30
million, and received mixed reviews from critics.
The film explores themes of loss of eyesight, opium,
biography, sioux, wild bill hickok.
The tone is emotional.